Guide to the Paper Tiger Television Records MSS.276
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VII. Video Productions, 1980-2014; 131.4 Linear Feet in 110 record cartons, 11 cassette boxes, 10 upright video containers, and 2 LP boxes.; 1000 U-matic; 339 MiniDV; 199 VHS; 108 Hi8; 46 Betacam_SP; 16 1_Inch_Video_Reel; 7 S-VHS; 4 Digital_Betacam; 2 DVCAM; 1 Betacam; 1 audiocassette; 2.06
  - Subseries VII.A: Broadcast Videos, 1981-2011
    - Rereading The Dragon -- Master, 1985 (Box 59, U-matic 276_0095)
    - Survey of Radical Periodicals with John Demeter and Tess Ewing, 1985
      - Master, 1985 (Box 166, U-matic 276_0078)
      - Dub master, undated (Box 138, U-matic 276_1347)
    - Youth and Media: Escape from Tom and Jerry, circa 1985
      - Master #2, undated (Box 156, U-matic 276_1691)
      - MiniDV recording, 1985; cuid4688 (Box 189, Minidv 276_1838)
        Duration: 29 Minutes 29 Seconds
    - How History Was Wounded / Elayne Rapping on Soap Operas, 1985-1990 (Box 70, Betacam sp 276_0252)
    - 100th Anniversary Show -- Safety master, January 9, 1986 (Box 164, U-matic 276_1775)
    - Aviation Weekly inserts for Lenny Siegel show, January 14, 1986 (Box 77, U-matic 276_0359)
    - Betsy Newman and Tom Murrin Read: "The Weekly World News", February 19, 1986
      - Master (Box 59, U-matic 276_0105)
      - Master (Box 60, U-matic 276_0106)
      - Master (Box 59, U-matic 276_0104)
    - On Location with Paper Tiger Television, July 26, 1986 (Box 71, U-matic 276_0260)
    - Joel Kovel Does El Tayacan, October 9, 1986 (Box 59, U-matic 276_0103)
    - Archie Singham On US Press and U.N. -- Master, 1986 (Box 59, U-matic 276_0101)
    - Ed Herman and The Famous Pope Plot: Who Dunnit?, 1986; cuid4697 (Box 170, U-matic 276_1841)
      Duration: 29 Minutes 09 Seconds
    - Far From America: Why Taiwan Loves Reagan, 1986
      - Dub master, undated (Box 162, U-matic 276_1756)
      - MiniDV recording, 1986 (Box 183, Minidv 276_1287)
    - Euro-American Soap Opera with Leonard Henny -- Master, 1986 (Box 59, U-matic 276_0097)
    - Getting a Grip on Access, 1986
      - U-matic recording (Box 74, U-matic 276_0321)
      - U-matic recording (Box 71, U-matic 276_0265)
    - International Working Women's Day -- ACTWV Master, 1986 (Box 59, U-matic 276_0102)
    - Josefina de Zayas and Isabel Larguia On Cuban Press, 1986 (Box 60, U-matic 276_0117)
    - Leonard Rifas Reads War Comics, 1986
      - Master (Box 60, U-matic 276_0107)
      - Edit master (Box 60, U-matic 276_0108)
    - Leonard Siegal Reads Aviation Week: Paper Tiger Takes to the Wild Blue Yonder, 1986; cuid4695 (Box 170, U-matic 276_1842)
    - Louis Freedberg Looks At South African Media: After the Media Blackout, 1986
      - Dub master (Box 60, U-matic 276_0112)
      - Master edit with mixed audio (Box 60, U-matic 276_0113)
    - Media in Cuba -- Master, 1986 (Box 60, U-matic 276_0118)
    - Michele Mattelart Reads The Chilean Press Avant Coup: "Every Day it Gets Harder to be a Good Housewife", 1986
      - #1 (Box 74, U-matic 276_0307)
      - Cutaways -- Movies, Les Femme de Pinodret (Box 74, U-matic 276_0308)
      - Dub master, cuid4696 (Box 170, U-matic 276_1845)
        Duration: 28 Minutes 44 Seconds
      - Final rough cut, last 30 minutes (Box 75, U-matic 276_0336)
    - Molly Kovel Reads Kiddy Books -- Master, 1986 (Box 59, U-matic 276_0094)
    - Nidia Bustos on MECATE: How Campesinos are Creating Theatre and Art in Revolutionary Nicaragua, 1986; cuid4694 (Box 171, U-matic 276_1846)
      Duration: 32 Minutes 20 Seconds
    - Noam Chomsky Reads The New York Times: "Seeking Peace In the Middle East", 1986; cuid4693
      - Dub (Box 171, U-matic 276_1848)
      - Rough footage (Box 171, U-matic 276_1849)
    - Paper Tiger TV Scans The (Inter) National Audio-Video Festival, 1986
      - Master, 1986 (Box 60, U-matic 276_0111)
      - With Joe Public music video, undated (Box 139, U-matic 276_1358)
    - Peter Wollen On The US Press, 1986 (Box 58, U-matic 276_0090)
    - Steve Schewel Introduces The North Carolina Independent: Progressive Newspaper Flourishes in the South, circa 1986
      - Dub master, undated (Box 154, U-matic 276_1671)
      - MiniDV recording, undated (Box 183, Minidv 276_1278)
      - VHS recording, undated (Box 163, Vhs 276_1764)
    - The Trial of Tilted Arc, 1986
      - Master (Box 58, U-matic ID: 276.0088)
      - Studio master (Box 58, U-matic ID: 276.0089)
    - Under Siege: Palestinians in the U.S. Media, 1986; cuid4698 (Box 170, U-matic 276_1844)
      Duration: 58 Minutes 06 Seconds
    - Under Siege: Palestinians in the U.S. Media / Vernon Walters: Portrait of a Terrorist -- Dub master, 1986 (Box 170, U-matic 276_1843)
    - Thulani Davis Asks Why Howard Beach?: Racial Violence and the Media, January 21, 1987; cuid4700 (Box 169, U-matic 276_1830)
      Duration: 30 Minutes
    - College Students Read College Dailies -- Master, off-air (unedited), January 28, 1987 (Box 71, U-matic 276_0261)
    - Janice Durald Reads: "Philadelphia Magazine", April 11, 1987
      - Tape 1 (Box 76, U-matic 276_0343)
      - Tape 2 (Box 76, U-matic 276_0345)
      - Master edit (Box 61, U-matic 276_0122)
    - Jill Macoska Dissects Popular Science Magazines and Beyond, April 15, 1987
      - Live master, 276_0114 (Box 166, U-matic 276_0114)
      - Master (Box 60, U-matic 276_0115)
    - "W"... Y?, April 29, 1987 (Box 60, U-matic 276_0120)
    - World What World! Cranky #2, April 30, 1987 (Box 76, U-matic 276_0337)
    - It Takes a Tough Ad Agency to Make a Tender Chicken -- Kathleen Hulser Debones the Poultry Industry, July 29, 1987
      - Original master (Box 157, U-matic 276_1705)
      - Original master #2 (Box 157, U-matic 276_1704)
      - Dub master "A", 1987; cuid4703 (Box 169, U-matic 276_1828)
        Duration: 29 Minutes 53 Seconds
    - Vinnie Mosco Goes Home Shopping -- Master, December 1987 (Box 62, U-matic 276_0137)
    - Animals in Mass Media: Images of a Schizophrenic Society -- Master, 1987 (Box 61, U-matic 276_0134)
    - Dan Hallin Watches The CBS Evening News, 1987
      - Master, 1987 (Box 61, U-matic 276_0125)
      - Dub, undated (Box 139, U-matic 276_1356)
    - Darrell Leo Reads Modern Bride, circa 1987
      - TBC dub master, undated (Box 139, U-matic 276_1357)
    - David Avalos Reads S.D. Union -- Master mix, 1987 (Box 61, U-matic 276_0126)
    - Dennis O'Neil reads Fanzines and The Rock 'n Roll Press, 1987
      - Master 1 (Box 61, U-matic 276_0124)
      - Master 2 (Box 75, U-matic 276_0335)
    - Donna Haraway Reads The National Geographic on Primates, 1987; cuid4702 (Box 169, U-matic 276_1829)
      Duration: 27 Minutes
    - Fashions Of The Times: Lorenn Glenn Davitian -- Master, 1987 (Box 62, U-matic 276_0139)
    - Herb Schiller Smashes the Crash, 1987
      - Dub master, 1987; cuid4705 (Box 172, U-matic 276_1856)
        Duration: 28 Minutes
      - Master, December 9, 1987 (Box 76, U-matic 276_0348)
      - U-matic recording, 1987 (Box 61, U-matic 276_0131)
    - Joel Kovel Shrinking of Amerika, 1987 (Box 60, U-matic 276_0119)
    - Lockport TV and Our Self Image -- Master, 1987 (Box 60, U-matic 276_0116)
    - Michael Chanan on Reuters: From Carrier Pigeons to Orbiting Birds, 1987; cuid4699 (Box 170, U-matic 176_1831)
      Duration: 28 Minutes 5 Seconds
    - Modern Bride -- Edit Master, 1987 (Box 61, U-matic 276_0132)
    - Neil Lazarus, Catherine Saalfield, and Kelly Anderson Read The Weekly Mail -- Edit master, 1987 (Box 62, U-matic 276_0147)
    - Not Top Gun: Chip Lorde Looks at the Hollywood Version of the Air Force, 1987
      - Sub-master, June 1987 (Box 61, U-matic 276_0123)
      - Dubbing master, 1987 (Box 80, U-matic 276_0395)
      - Dub -- Preview only, undated (Box 139, U-matic 276_1359)
    - Oliver's Army: What Wasn't Heard in the Hearings with Eric Mendelsohn -- Master, 1987 (Box 61, U-matic 276_0133)
    - PTTV Invades "Amerika", 1987; cuid4701 (Box 169, U-matic 276_1823)
      Dub from Submaster; Duration: 29 Minutes 6 Seconds
    - P.W.A.C. Talks Back! -- New edited master, 1987 (Box 61, U-matic 276_0135)
    - Red Ink: Rebecca Zurier Reads The Masses, 1987; cuid4704 (Box 169, U-matic 276_1827)
    - Robbie Conal Plasters Manhattan -- Edit master, 1987 (Box 62, U-matic 276_0146)
    - Shelia Row Botham Reads The Star -- Edit master, 1987 (Box 61, U-matic 276_0130)
    - World? What World? Keeping America Dis Informed: The World According to the U.S. Media -- Master for CH4 in the U.K., 1987 (Box 61, U-matic 276_0121)
    - Special recording off SATCOM 3R, Transponder 7, July 12, 1988 (Box 71, U-matic 276_0263)
    - The Bicentennial Will Not Be Televised! -- Master, 1988 (Box 63, U-matic 276_0151)
    - Born To Be Sold: Martha Rosler Reads The Strange Case of Baby S/M, 1988
      - Original edit master (Box 62, U-matic 276_0148)
      - Public access master (Box 62, U-matic 276_0149)
    - The Campaign Miniseries with Daniel Marcus -- Edit master, 1988 (Box 62, U-matic 276_0145)
    - Campaign Miniseries: Daniel Marcus Watches the Election, 1988
      - MiniDV recording (Box 182, Minidv 276_1232)
      - MiniDV recording (Box 183, Minidv 276_1264)
    - CBS Tries the New York Three (NY3): Racist Lies on Prime Time TV, 1988; cuid4708 (Box 176, U-matic 276_1897)
    - Fred Landis Digests Selecciones, 1988; cuid4706
      - Dub master (Box 172, U-matic 276_1862)
      - Edit (Box 172, U-matic 276_1861)
    - Jim Kavanagh discusses Fighting Brothers: Black/White Unity in Popular American Culture, 1988
      - Edit master (Box 62, U-matic 276_0140)
      - U-matic recording (Box 80, U-matic 276_0405)
    - Getting Away With Murder: Northern Ireland and the U.S. Media -- Studio master, 1988 (Box 61, U-matic 276_0129)
    - Gloria House Reads: The Detroit Free Press, 1988; cuid4707 (Box 174, U-matic 276_1878)
    - Sock Ads: Judith Williamson Consumes Passionately in Southern California, 1988
      - Dub master, 276_0128 (Box 166, U-matic 276_0128)
      - U-matic recording (Box 61, U-matic 276_0127)
      - U-matic recording (Box 75, U-matic 276_0333)
    - Michael Harrington Looks At Democracy -- Master, 1988 (Box 62, U-matic 276_0142)
    - Militarism in America After Platoon, 1988
      - Edit master (Box 62, U-matic 276_0144)
      - U-matic recording, 1988 (Box 62, U-matic 276_0143)
    - The Pedagogy of Telecommunications: Teaching TV with Media Professors from around The Nation, 1988
      - Edit master, undated (Box 114, U-matic 276_0696)
      - Unedited master, 1988 (Box 62, U-matic 276_0141)
    - Satellite as Witness, circa 1988
      - Master, original, undated (Box 113, U-matic 276_0692)
      - Betacam SP recording, undated (Box 159, Betacam sp 276_1729)
    - Simon Watney Says No to Section 28, 1988
      - U-matic recording, December 1988 (Box 75, U-matic 276_0332)
      - U-matic recording, 1988 (Box 62, U-matic 276_0150)
    - Transformer AIDS, 1988; cuid4710 (Box 176, U-matic 276_1898)
      Duration: 30 Minutes 44 Seconds
    - Vinnie Mosco Goes Home Shopping -- Master 2, 1988 (Box 62, U-matic 276_0138)
    - William Kunstler Reads The U.S. Constitution, 1988
      - Master, November 18, 1987 (Box 76, U-matic 276_0350)
      - Cutaways, November 18, 1987 (Box 76, U-matic 276_0351)
      - Master, 1988; cuid39072 (Box 62, U-matic 276_0136)
      - Betacam SP recording, October 24, 1990 (Box 69, Betacam sp 276_0244)
    - Iran Show, October 29, 1989
      - Camera one, Tape three (Box 108, U-matic 276_0601)
      - Camera two, Tape two -- Kelly (Box 107, U-matic 276_0600)
    - Operation Unjust Cause: Robert Knight and P.T.T.V Look At The Illegal Invasion Of Panama, December 20, 1989; cuid4721 (Box 172, U-matic 276_1857)
      Duration: 29 Minutes
    - Daniel del Solar Looks at PBS, 1989
      - A-camera -- Dub from master, June 30, 1989 (Box 76, U-matic 276_0346)
      - B-camera -- Bump from 8mm camera original, June 30, 1989 (Box 75, U-matic 276_0334)
    - Desperately Seeking Reality: Herb Schiller Reads Trash TV / From Woodstock to Tiananmen Square: Ted Koppel's Long March, 1989 (Box 69, Betacam sp 276_0243)
    - Felt Evidence: Investigating Reproductive Technologies, 1989; cuid4709 (Box 174, U-matic 276_1877)
    - Fighting the Fundamentalist Fig Leaf, 1989
      - Master (Box 63, U-matic 276_0156)
      - Edit master (Box 63, U-matic 276_0157)
      - Edit master -- Short version (Box 63, U-matic 276_0158)
    - Flo Kennedy on Access, June 1989
      - Uncut original master, June 16, 1989 (Box 71, U-matic 276_0262)
      - Edit master, June 20, 1989 (Box 72, U-matic 276_0282)
    - Fred Landis Reads The Washington Times: The Dark Side of the Moonies, 1989; cuid4714 (Box 174, U-matic 276_1885)
      Duration: 29 Minutes 48 Seconds
    - From Woodstock To Tiananmen Square: Ted Koppel's Long March, 1989; cuid4717 (Box 174, U-matic 276_1882)
      Duration: 26 Minutes 57 Seconds
    - Greg Ulmer on Telerevisioning Literacy -- Master, 1989 (Box 63, U-matic 276_0153)
    - The Image at the End of the Tunnel: Vietnam Nostalgia Grips the U.S. Media -- Edit master, 1989 (Box 63, U-matic 276_0154)
    - Just Say Yes: Kathy High Looks at Marketing Legal Drugs, 1989
      - Dub master, 1989; cuid4713 (Box 174, U-matic 276_1880)
        Duration: 28 Minutes 55 Seconds
      - MiniDV recording, 1989 (Box 183, Minidv 276_1277)
    - Martin Lucas Watches "No" Video: The Chilean Plebiscite on TV -- Edit Master, 1989 (Box 63, U-matic 276_0155)
    - Page Dubois Reads Plato, 1989 (Box 63, U-matic 276_0152)
    - Smurfs. Toys R U.S. Mark Dion, 1989 (Box 63, U-matic 276_0159)
    - Television Across Borders with Michael Silverman, 1989; cuid4715 (Box 174, U-matic 276_1884)
      Duration: 26 Minutes 25 Seconds
    - Terry Odendahl's Glamour Workout, 1989; cuid4712 (Box 174, U-matic 276_1879)
    - Williamsburg Bridge Demo, Anti-Incinerator Demo and March -- Interviews, early 1990s (Box 82, Vhs 276_0454)
    - Torn Between Colors: Youth and the Media Through Our Eyes Video and History Project, Bronx Satellite High School, January 16, 1990 (Box 63, U-matic 276_0160)
    - Access Demo -- Time-Life Headquarters #1, David Shulman, May 2, 1990 (Box 72, U-matic 276_0284)
    - Herb Schiller Reads Whittle -- Master, May 17, 1990 (Box 144, U-matic 276_0941)
    - This is A Sex Advertisement: PTTV Reads the Catholic Bishops' PR Campaign, May 23, 1990
      - Studio tape (Box 74, U-matic 276_0320)
      - U-matic recording (Box 64, U-matic 276_0167)
    - Graphics -- Middle East Show, September 1990 (Box 73, U-matic 276_0304)
    - PTTV Special on Middle East with Coalition to Stop U.S. Intervention in Middle East, September 20, 1990 (Box 64, U-matic 276_0170)
    - Operation Oil Shield: PTTV Responds to Middle East Crisis with the Coalition to Stop U.S. Intervention, September 1990
      - Dub master (Box 138, U-matic 276_1345)
      - Dub (Box 138, U-matic 276_1344)
    - Special on the Situation in the Middle East, September 26, 1990 (Box 139, U-matic 276_1354)
    - Nolan Bowie Reads About Privacy / Animals in the Mass Media -- New dubmaster, October 13, 1990 (Box 69, Betacam sp 276_0248)
    - Mid-East Show -- Metro Access, November 9, 1990
      - Master (Box 108, U-matic 276_0596)
      - U-matic recording (Box 121, U-matic 276_0858)
      - U-matic recording (Box 123, U-matic 276_0872)
    - Joan Does Dynasty / Sock Ads, November 12, 1990 (Box 70, Betacam sp 276_0251)
    - Middle East Show II: Paper Tiger Smashes the Oiligarchies -- Edit master, November 28, 1990 (Box 108, U-matic 276_0595)
    - Ads! Ads! Ads! Mark Crispin Miller -- Edit Master, 1990 (Box 64, U-matic 276_0177)
    - Armond White Analyzes Do The Write Thing: Critical Advocacy, 1990
      - Master, 1990 (Box 63, U-matic ID: 276.0162)
      - Master, undated (Box 114, U-matic 276_0697)
    - Herb Schiller vs. the Bat Lords of the Global Village -- Edited master, 1990 (Box 64, U-matic 276_0166)
    - Daily News: New York's Hometown Strike -- Edit master, 1990 (Box 64, U-matic 276_0175)
    - Drawing the Line at Pittston, 1990
      - Master edit (Box 63, U-matic ID: 276.0165)
      - U-matic recording (Box 63, U-matic ID: 276.0164)
    - Going for the Green: Bill Winberg Looks at the Corporate Marketing of Earth Day and Environmentalism, 1990 (Box 64, U-matic 276_0168)
    - Gulf Crisis TV Project Series, 1990-1991
      - War, Oil, and Power, circa 1990 (Box 168, U-matic 276_1818)
      - War, Oil, and Power / Operation Dissidence, 1990-1991
        - Dub master, 1990; cuid4725 (Box 168, U-matic 276_1817)
        - Edit master, January 7-9, 1991 (Box 191, 1 inch video reel 276_0665)
        - MiniDV recording, undated (Box 182, Minidv 276_1208)
      - Operation Dissidence, 1990; cuid4726
        - Edit master #2, undated (Box 137, U-matic 276_1337)
        - U-matic recording, undated (Box 168, U-matic 276_1816)
        - U-matic recording, undated (Box 15)
      - Getting Out of the Sand Trap, 1990; cuid4727
        - Dub master (Box 175, U-matic 276_1895)
        - Video recording (Box 15)
      - Bring the Troops Home!, 1990; cuid4728 (Box 175, U-matic 276_1894)
      - Manufacturing the Enemy, circa 1990
        - Protection master, undated (Box 193, 1 inch video reel 276_1795)
        - Master, February 26-28, 1991 (Box 197, 1 inch video reel 276_0671)
        - U-matic recording, 1990; cuid4730 (Box 169, U-matic 276_1822)
          Duration: 30 Minutes 15 Seconds
      - Just Say No!, 1990-1991
        - Protection master, March 10, 1991 (Box 199, 1 inch video reel 276_0669)
        - Master, March 10, 1991 (Box 196, 1 inch video reel 276_0672)
        - Dub master, 1990; cuid4733 (Box 166, U-matic 276_1808)
      - News World Order, 1991; cuid4729
        - Dub master, undated (Box 176, U-matic 276_1896)
        - International TV version, undated (Box 133, U-matic 276_1137)
        - Master, undated (Box 191, 1 inch video reel 276_0664)
        - Master, February 22, 1991 (Box 198, 1 inch video reel 276_0670)
        - Sequence master, undated (Box 124, U-matic 276_0743)
        - Video recording, undated (Box 14, Media 204)
      - War on the Home Front, circa 1990-1991; cuid4734
        - Dub master, undated (Box 166, U-matic 276_1807)
        - PBS master, undated (Box 192, 1 inch video reel 276_1793)
        - Protection master, undated (Box 194, 1 inch video reel 276_1796)
        - Segment one -- Rough cut, undated (Box 103, U-matic 276_0533)
        - Video recording, undated (Box 16)
      - Global Dissent, 1990
        - Master, undated (Box 190, 1 inch video reel 276_0663)
        - Master, undated (Box 200, 1 inch video reel 276_0668)
        - Dub, 1990; cuid4732 (Box 166, U-matic 276_1809)
        - U-matic recording, undated (Box 127, U-matic 276_1097)
      - Lines in the Sand, circa 1990
        - Protection master, undated (Box 195, 1 inch video reel 276_1797)
        - Master, undated (Box 191, 1 inch video reel 276_0666)
        - Doc footage, undated (Box 127, U-matic 276_1098)
        - U-matic recording, 1990; cuid4731 (Box 169, U-matic 276_1821)
      - Dateline: United Nations -- Master edit, undated (Box 133, U-matic 276_1134)
      - Excerpt -- Master, undated (Box 110, U-matic 276_0621)
      - Let the People Speak, undated (Box 134, U-matic 276_1139)
      - Trust Me! -- Submaster media edit, undated (Box 134, U-matic 276_1140)
      - The Wrath of Grapes, Fighting for Our Lives, undated (Box 182, Minidv 276_1206)
      - Vampire Pigs of Congress, undated (Box 134, U-matic 276_1144)
      - Youth Rap Groups, Interviews with Students, undated (Box 133, U-matic 276_1133)
      - U-matic recording, undated (Box 127, U-matic 276_1091)
    - How History Was Wounded: An Exclusive Report on Taiwanese Media, 1990; cuid4716 (Box 174, U-matic 276_1883)
    - International Working Women's Day 1990 (Box 63, U-matic 276_0163)
    - Intervention Into A Field of Dreams, 1990; cuid4719
      - Dub master (Box 175, U-matic 276_1893)
      - Video recording (Box 14, Media 183)
    - Kids Views on News: Carla Seal-Wanner and Children's Express Watch TV News, 1990
      - Dub master (Box 64, U-matic 276_0172)
      - Edit master (Box 64, U-matic 276_0171)
    - Notes On Zimbabwe, 1990; cuid4718
    - Panama -- Edit Master, 1990 (Box 64, U-matic 276_0176)
    - The Road To Mississippi: "Reclaiming Our History" by the Through Our Eyes Video History Project, 1990; cuid21490 (Box 175, U-matic 276_1890)
    - Robin Andersen Exposes the Real-Deal: CIA-Contra-Cocaine, 1990
      - Edit master, 1990 (Box 64, U-matic 276_0174)
      - Master (Box 74, U-matic 276_0313)
      - Single camera on Robin Andersen, November 1987 (Box 74, U-matic 276_0312)
    - The Silence That Silences, Robert Kinney, 1990 (Box 64, U-matic 276_0173)
    - Torn Between Colors: Youth and the Media, circa 1990
      - Camera original, undated (Box 157, U-matic 276_1708)
      - Dub, Final edit, undated (Box 138, U-matic 276_1342)
    - Troops Out Now! Middle East Special -- Dub, 1990 (Box 139, U-matic 276_1353)
    - TV Turn On: Stepping Up to the Electronic Soapbox, 1990
      - Credits, NYCCRM at City Hall, statements (Box 74, U-matic 276_0309)
      - Dub (Box 72, U-matic 276_0283)
      - Public access show, 1990 (Box 64, U-matic 276_0178)
    - The Underground Voices of the Panamanian People, 1990
      - VHS recording, April 5, 1990 (Box 124, Vhs 276_0775)
      - VHS recording, undated (Box 124, Vhs 276_0774)
    - Unpacking Ted Koppel's Revolution in a Box: Revolution? What a Crock! -- Edited master, 1990 (Box 65, U-matic 276_0195)
    - U.S. Bans Abortion Title Ten Restrictions: A Policy That Kills, 1990 (Box 64, U-matic 276_0169)
    - Zero Tolerance: J Tony Serra Cross-examines the "War on Drugs" -- PTTV West, 1990 (Box 63, U-matic 276_0161)
    - Access-Able World? What World? -- Edit master with unmixed audio, 1987-1991 (Box 65, U-matic 276_0181)
    - Carlos Fernando Charmorro Reads Barricada, 1991
      - Original (Box 76, U-matic 276_0347)
      - Master (Box 65, U-matic 276_0182)
    - Veterans Speak Out, February 1991
      Produced by Paper Tiger West, San Francisco
      - Part one, February 9, 1991 (Box 104, U-matic 276_0540)
      - Part two, February 2, 1991 (Box 76, U-matic 276_0339)
    - Give Peace a Chant, February, 1991 (Box 118, U-matic 276_0810)
    - Herb Schiller, March 1991 (Box 82, Hi8 276_0441)
    - Transformer AIDS with Bob Kinney / Felt Evidence, April 17, 1991 (Box 70, Betacam sp 276_0256)
    - Desperately Seeking Reality: Herb Schiller Reads Trash TV, April 19, 1991; cuid4711 (Box 174, U-matic 276_1881)
      Duration: 31 Minutes 19 Seconds
    - Access Denied -- Rough cut, April 29, 1991 (Box 148, U-matic 276_0991)
    - Varda Burstyn Reads Playboy / Rereading the Dragon, August 13, 1991 (Box 70, Betacam sp 276_0249)
    - Bill Boddy Reads the 1934 Communications Act / Brian Winston Reads TV Guide, August 28, 1991 (Box 69, Betacam sp 276_0247)
    - Renee Tajima Reads Asian Images / Herb Schiller Reads The NYT #4: Hanging Out in Foreign Capitals, September 21, 1991 (Box 81, Betacam sp 276_0415)
    - Richie Perez Reads Fort Apapche / Teresa Costa Reads Biker Lifestyle, October 3, 1991 (Box 69, Betacam sp 276_0246)
    - Joel Kovel Reads Bill Moyers -- New edit master (with Mutiny Tag), October 23, 1991 (Box 65, U-matic 276_0183)
    - L.R. Beltran Tunes in Bolivian Miners' Radio - Edited master, November 10, 1991 (Box 65, U-matic 276_0185)
    - Aiesha and Other Stories from Palestine, 1991 (Box 105, Vhs 276_0561)
    - Collateral Damage, 1991
      - Master, 1991 (Box 65, U-matic 276_0186)
      - Part two -- Dub, undated (Box 139, U-matic 276_1352)
    - Gulf Crisis Updates, 1991, undated
      - Update #2, San Francisco, undated (Box 124, U-matic 276_0780)
      - Update #6, undated (Box 119, U-matic 276_0832)
      - Update #7, February 25, 1991 (Box 168, U-matic 276_1820)
      - Update #9, undated (Box 168, U-matic 276_1819)
    - Judith Mayne Reads Soap Opera Magazines, 1991